(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],[,,,,function(e,n,t){e.exports=t(11)},,,,,function(e,n,t){},function(e,n,t){},function(e,n,t){"use strict";t.r(n);var a=t(0),s=t.n(a),r=t(3),o=t.n(r),c=(t(9),t(1));t(10);var i=function(e){return s.a.createElement("h2",null,"Question ",e.current," of ",e.total)};var l=function(e){return s.a.createElement("h1",null,e.question)};var u=function(e){var n=["answer"];return e.selected&&n.push("selected"),s.a.createElement("button",{value:e.letter,className:n.join(" "),onClick:e.handleClick},s.a.createElement("span",{className:"letter"},e.letter,"."),e.answer)};var d=function(e){return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement(u,{letter:"a",answer:e.question.answer_a,handleClick:e.handleClick,selected:"a"===e.currentAnswer}),s.a.createElement(u,{letter:"b",answer:e.question.answer_b,handleClick:e.handleClick,selected:"b"===e.currentAnswer}),s.a.createElement(u,{letter:"c",answer:e.question.answer_c,handleClick:e.handleClick,selected:"c"===e.currentAnswer}),s.a.createElement(u,{letter:"d",answer:e.question.answer_d,handleClick:e.handleClick,selected:"d"===e.currentAnswer}))},w=[{id:1,question:"Which statement about Hooks is not true?",answer_a:"Hooks are 100% backwards-compatible and can be used side by side with classes",answer_b:"Hooks are still in beta and not available yet",answer_c:"Hooks are completely opt-in, there's no need to rewrite existing code",answer_d:"All of the above",correct_answer:"b"},{id:2,question:"Which one is not a Hook?",answer_a:"useState()",answer_b:"useConst()",answer_c:"useReducer()",answer_d:"All of the above",correct_answer:"b"},{id:3,question:"What Hook should be used for data fetching?",answer_a:"useDataFetching()",answer_b:"useApi()",answer_c:"useEffect()",answer_d:"useRequest()",correct_answer:"c"},{id:4,question:"What are Hooks?",answer_a:'Hooks let you "hook" into a class component to set state.',answer_b:"New way of doing the same thing. Instead of function methods, we use classes.",answer_c:"Hooks let you use function components to manage state, instead of class components.",answer_d:"Hooks let you make your code more complex and confusing.",correct_answer:"c"},{id:4,question:"Which is not a React Hooks rule?",answer_a:"Only call hooks at the top level.",answer_b:"Only call Hooks from React classes.",answer_c:"Don't call hooks inside loops, conditions or nested functions.",answer_d:"Only hooks from React function components",correct_answer:"c"}],h=[{id:1,question:"Which statement about the Agile methodology is true?",answer_a:"Agile emphasizes incremental delivery, continual planning, and continual learning.",answer_b:"Agile is best for projects with well-defined requirements where no changes are expected.",answer_c:"In Agile development all deliverable are delivered after the product is finished.",answer_d:"All of the above",correct_answer:"a"},{id:2,question:"Which one is true about Synchronous vs Asynchronous?",answer_a:"Asynchronous means only one execution at a time.",answer_b:"Synchronous means more than one thing can synchronize and run at the same time.",answer_c:"Synchronous basically means only one thing can execute at once.",answer_d:"All of the above",correct_answer:"c"},{id:3,question:"Which is true about Web Services(API) SOAP vs REST?",answer_a:"Rest was created to address the problems of SOAP.",answer_b:"REST is a protocol whereas SOAP is an architectural pattern.",answer_c:"REST uses service interfaces to expose its functionality to client applications while SOAP uses Uniform Service locators to access the components on the hardware device.",answer_d:"REST needs more bandwidth for its usage whereas SOAP doesn't need much bandwidth.",correct_answer:"a"}],m=[{id:1,question:"What is the name of Stephen's dog?",answer_a:"Finn",answer_b:"Jake",answer_c:"Fluffy",answer_d:"He doesn't have a dog",correct_answer:"b"},{id:2,question:"When is Stephen's birthday?",answer_a:"January 1, 1990",answer_b:"Febuary 12, 1992",answer_c:"April 21, 1992",answer_d:"He wasn't born",correct_answer:"c"},{id:3,question:"How many siblings does Stephen have?",answer_a:"1",answer_b:"2",answer_c:"3",answer_d:"4",correct_answer:"c"}];var b=function(){var e=Object(a.useState)(0),n=Object(c.a)(e,2),t=n[0],r=n[1],o=Object(a.useState)(""),u=Object(c.a)(o,2),b=u[0],_=u[1],f=Object(a.useState)([]),p=Object(c.a)(f,2),k=p[0],v=p[1],y=Object(a.useState)(!1),E=Object(c.a)(y,2),g=E[0],S=E[1],q=Object(a.useState)(""),A=Object(c.a)(q,2),O=A[0],C=A[1],j=Object(a.useState)(!1),H=Object(c.a)(j,2),N=H[0],W=H[1],R=Object(a.useState)(w),x=Object(c.a)(R,2),I=x[0],P=x[1],z=I[t];return N?g?s.a.createElement("div",{className:"container results"},s.a.createElement("h2",null,"Results"),s.a.createElement("ul",null,k.map((function(e){var n=I.find((function(n){return n.id===e.questionId}));return s.a.createElement("div",{key:n.id},n.question," - ",function(e,n){return e.correct_answer===n.answer?s.a.createElement("span",{className:"correct"},"Correct"):s.a.createElement("span",{className:"failed"},"Incorrect")}(n,e))}))),s.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary",onClick:function(){v([]),_(""),r(0),S(!1),W(!1)}},"Back to quiz select")):s.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},s.a.createElement(i,{total:I.length,current:t+1}),s.a.createElement(l,{question:z.question}),function(){if(O)return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"error"},O)}(),s.a.createElement(d,{question:z,currentAnswer:b,handleClick:function(e){_(e.target.value),C("")}}),s.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary",onClick:function(){var e={questionId:z.id,answer:b};b?(k.push(e),v(k),_(""),console.log(b),t+1<I.length?r(t+1):S(!0)):C("Please setect an answer.")}},"Submit")):s.a.createElement("div",{className:"container results"},s.a.createElement("h2",null,"Select a Quiz"),s.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary",onClick:function(){W(!0),P(I)}},"React Hooks"),s.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary",onClick:function(){W(!0),P(h)}},"General"),s.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary",onClick:function(){W(!0),P(m)}},"Silly"))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));o.a.render(s.a.createElement(s.a.StrictMode,null,s.a.createElement(b,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}],[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.19962247.chunk.js.map